<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on George Dolias</title>
    <link>https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on George Dolias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Guaranteed TSP solutions in VLSI</title>
      <link>https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/post/project-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/post/project-15/</guid>
      <description>In this project, I implemented approaches that perform near-optimal combination of MOS transistors onto Integrated circuits, a process called Very Large Scale Inegration (VLSI). The process of VLSI was examined by using approaches of the known combinatorial optimization problem called Traveling Salesperson Problem (TSP). TSP is described as follows:   Given a set of cities and the distance between each pair of cities, what is the shortest possible tour that visits each city exactly once, and returns to the starting city?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Near-Optimal TSP solutions in VLSI</title>
      <link>https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/post/project-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/post/project-14/</guid>
      <description>In this project, I implemented approaches that perform near-optimal combination of MOS transistors onto Integrated circuits, a process called Very Large Scale Inegration (VLSI). The process of VLSI was examined by using approaches of the known combinatorial optimization problem called Traveling Salesperson Problem (TSP). TSP is described as follows:   Given a set of cities and the distance between each pair of cities, what is the shortest possible tour that visits each city exactly once, and returns to the starting city?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimal TSP solutions in VLSI</title>
      <link>https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/post/project-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/post/project-13/</guid>
      <description>In this project, I implemented approaches that perform optimal combination of MOS transistors onto Integrated circuits, a process called Very Large Scale Inegration (VLSI). The process of VLSI was examined by using approaches of the known combinatorial optimization problem called Traveling Salesperson Problem (TSP). TSP is described as follows:   Given a set of cities and the distance between each pair of cities, what is the shortest possible tour that visits each city exactly once, and returns to the starting city?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploratory Data Analysis and Machine Learning with medical data</title>
      <link>https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/post/project-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgiosdolias.github.io/portfolio/post/project-16/</guid>
      <description>Recent advancements in data science render scientists capable of sorting, managing and analyzing large amounts of data more effectively and efficiently. One of the sectors where these new technologies have been applied is the healthcare industry, which is increasingly becoming more data-reliant due to vast quantities of patient and medical data. As a result, medical practices and patient care are significantly improved.
 In this notebook, we will implement various techniques regarding the Exploratory Data Analysis (EDA) of medical data from different datasets and train various machine learning models for the prediction of important medical factors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>